(Leonard:)Guys, everyone is involved
in this, okay?
(Leonard:)Howard's invention,
(Amy:)Sheldon's math,
my original theory
(Leonard:)that space-time was like
a supercooled liquid.
(Leonard:)Which I'm sure
Penny would've mentioned
(Leonard:)if she wasn't working
on that hangnail right now.
(Amy:)What?
(Howard:)Honey, this is fine.
(Bernadette:)If you want to sign a contract
that Sheldon whipped up,
(Bernadette:)go ahead.
(Howard:)Can I talk to you in the hall?
(Penny:)Sure.
Excuse us.
(Sheldon:)Hey, Leonard.
What?
(Sheldon:)If she doesn't think that
we should apply for this patent,
(Sheldon:)she's being patently absurd.
(Leonard:)Good one.
(Sheldon:)Okay, you got it.
(Sheldon:)See, I was afraid
it was a thinker.
(Howard:)What are you doing?
I just want to make sure
(Bernadette:)you've thought this through.
(Howard:)What's to think about?
We have an invention
(Howard:)and want to move forward.
(Bernadette:)Howie, you're about
to form a legal partnership
(Bernadette:)with Sheldon Cooper.